

# PE HAO CHEAH

No 8, Jalan PU 2/7, ↑
Taman Puchong Utama,
47100 Puchong, Selangor
016-3313-878 **\** 

cheahpehao@gmail.com



#### INTRODUCTION

I am a 25-year-old Malaysian that graduated from **Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR)** after finishing my degree — **Bachelor of Science (Hons) Game Development** with a graduating **CGPA** of **2.90**.

I am computer literate, and a fast learner. I can work under stressful situation, and I love challenges in work as it pushes me to become better. I am very eager and willing to learn new things. I am also able to adapt to a new working environment quickly.

My native language is Mandarin Chinese, but I can also speak fluent English, and communicate well in Bahasa Malaysia. I can also understand Cantonese and Hokkien dialects as well.



#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Science (Hons) Game Development @ Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR)

MAY 2015 – MAY 2018

I finished my studies with a final CGPA of 2.90. My top subjects are Web Application Development, Computer Graphics using OpenGL and Mobile Game Developments.

## Senior Middle Three (Science Stream) @ Chong Hwa Independent High School Kuala Lumpur (CHKL)

JANUARY 2009 – DECEMBER 2014

Graduated my six-years secondary education with 2As in UEC, and 3As in SPM with Bahasa Malaysia and Sejarah scoring B+ and B respectively.



#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

### IT Admin cum Project Executive | Han Culture Centre (M) Sdn Bhd JULY 2018 – MAY 2021

I was responsible for the design and development of my company's website.

Besides that, I was also responsible to provide level 1 and level 2 technical support by handling and resolving day-to-day computer hardware and software related issues that the company staffs encountered.

At the meantime, I also handle Chinese Proficiency Test (HSK) administrative works and execution.

#### Intern as Android Developer | Globaltium Sdn Bhd

#### JUNE 2017 – AUGUST 2017

My responsibility is to develop native Android application using Android Studio that the client asked. I must coordinate and cooperate with the designers and the backend developers. During the internship, I have involved in the development of two Android application and exposed to the Android application development environment.

#### IT Assistant | Chong Hwa Independent High School (CHKL)

JANUARY 2015 - MAY 2015

My responsibility is to provide helpdesk and level 1 technical support to the teachers with computer hardware and software related issues such as troubleshooting to identify the issue with their computer and provide a solution for them.



#### **SKILLS**

#### **Language Proficiency**

Language	Speaking	Writing
Mandarin	Excellent	Excellent
English	Fluent	Fluent
Malay	Fairly Fluently	Fluent
Cantonese	Intermediate	-
Hokkien	Intermediate	-

#### **Programming Language and Tools Proficiency**

#### Other skills:

- Computer literate
- Fast learner
- Quick at adapting to new environment
- Responsible on my work